(Leonard:)I don't care.
Wrong! Hunt's!
Hey, Amy!
What do you say?
(Sheldon:)You ready to move on
to the mustard round?
(Amy:)Have you not noticed that
I've been sitting back here
(Amy:)quietly stewing for
the past two hours?
(Sheldon:)I just thought
you were bad at the game.
I'm mad at you!
(Amy:)How could you just
go away like that
(Amy:)without even
saying good-bye,
(Amy:)and then call Leonard
for help instead of me?
Amy?
(Sheldon:)May I please have
a moment of privacy
(Sheldon:)to speak with my roommate?
We're in a moving car!
(Amy:)What do you expect me to do?
(Amy:)Stick my fingers in my ears?
(Sheldon:)Well, I was thinking
put your head out the window
(Sheldon:)like a dog, but that'll work.
(Sheldon:)Please? This'll be quick.
(Sheldon:)Leonard?